welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we're going to be talking about
我们将要讨论的视频
transparency and the Alpha Channel in
中的透明度和Alpha通道
so transparency lets us erase and
因此 透明度让我们擦除和
not see any pixels not white not black
看不到任何像素不是白色也不是黑色
just a clear transparent pixel so if we
只有一个透明的像素 所以如果我们
want to do that now we've learned in the
现在我们已经在
past if we clicked on the erase tool and
如果我们点击擦除工具并
we left click and hold it will erase
我们左键点击并按住它就会被删除
parts of our image well right now this
我们形象的一部分现在就是这个
image does not have an alpha Channel
图像没有Alpha通道
which means it's only going to do solid
这意味着它只会做得很扎实
pixels or solid
像素或实心
yeah.well solid pixels even white is a
是啊 纯色像素即使是白色也是
solid pixel what I mean by that is if
纯像素我的意思是如果
we're if we were to erase this corner
如果我们要抹去这个角落
right here and then export this image we
就在这里 然后导出这个图像 我们
would see it just like we do now so this
会像我们现在一样看到它 所以这个
part that we erased wouldn't be clear it
我们抹去的部分不会很清楚
wouldn't be like glass like showing
不会像玻璃一样展示
through to what's behind it like it
直到它背后的东西就像它
would be I downloaded the icon
会是我下载了图标
right here so the icon has
就在这里 所以图标有
transparency we can tell that because it
透明度我们可以这样说 因为它
has this checker pattern this is sort of
有这个棋盘格图案 这是一种
the the way that you can see if
你能看到的方式就是
something is transparent or not so this
有些东西是透明的 或者不是这样的
is telling us everywhere where we can
告诉我们哪里有我们可以去的地方
see a pixel where we can see a color or
看到一个像素 我们可以看到一种颜色或
we can see the outline of this we know
我们可以看到这一点的轮廓 我们知道
that the actual image is there but
真实的图像就在那里 但是
everywhere where it shows these squares
所有显示这些方块的地方
this checker pattern that's basically
这种棋盘格模式基本上是
clear or glass or transparency and
透明或玻璃或透明的和
that's why when we zoom in here to this
这就是为什么当我们放大到这里的时候
actual icon we are we look at it on the
我们是真实的图标我们看着它在
desktop and we see as we move it around
桌面 当我们移动它时 我们会看到
see it we can see it it's green
看到它了我们可以看到它是绿色的
background over here now and over here
背景现在在这里 在这里
we can if we drag it over top of another
如果我们把它拖到另一个上面 我们就可以
icon it's transparent so this real image
图标它是透明的 所以这张真实的图像
is actually a complete square image like
实际上是一个完整的正方形图像 如
this but we're only seeing this shape
但是我们只看到了这个形状
and a lot of times people get confused
很多时候 人们会感到困惑
when they're first starting out with
当他们第一次开始
because they want to create a
因为他们想要创建一个
circle or something well that's how you
圆圈之类的好吧 你就是这样的
do it is you have to have transparency
做到这一点是你必须有透明度
so to get transparency right now we're
因此 为了提高透明度 我们现在
erasing but we're getting white we might
正在抹去 但我们可能会变白
as well be just draw like painting white
不如就像画白一样画
on top of this it's kind of the same as
最重要的是 它有点像
erasing through to white it's kind of
把它擦成白色 有点像
hard to tell a difference so I'm gonna
很难区分 所以我要
hit control Z a couple of times to add
按下控件Z几次即可添加
an alpha channel we can look over here
我们可以在这里查看的Alpha通道
sometimes you can have a separate
有时你可以有一个单独的
background
背景
but the easiest way to do this is to
但要做到这一点 最简单的方法是
just come over here in this area and
只要到这一区来 然后
right-click and then go down to add
右键单击 然后向下转至添加
alpha channel and what that's going to
Alpha通道以及这将会带来什么
do we don't notice any changes right
我们没有注意到任何变化吗？
away but when we try to erase now we see
离开 但当我们试图抹去 现在我们看到
it's not white we see we're erasing true
它不是白色的 我们看到我们在抹去真实
into that true transparency I can erase
变成我可以抹去的真正的透明
parts of my face I can erase whatever I
我的脸的一部分我可以抹去我的任何东西
want so let's try and do some erasing
想要所以让我们试着擦掉一些
here real quick let me make my brush a
这里真的很快让我把我的刷子
little bit larger and I'm just going to
再大一点 我就会
erase kind of quickly some of the
很快就会抹去一些
background here looks like I got part of
这里的背景看起来像是我得到了
myself that's okay
我自己 那没问题
and I'll go file export because I want
我要去出口文件 因为我想
to show you when you're exporting with
要在使用导出时向您显示
transparency it's also important that
透明度也很重要
you save the file as a PNG and not a
您将文件另存为PNG 而不是
JPEG a jpg file if we did a jpg I'll
Jpg文件如果我们做了jpg 我会
just show you what'll happen so we have
只要让你看看会发生什么 我们就有
test jpg we'll export that to the
测试jpg 我们将把它导出到
desktop and we'll go and take a look at
桌面 我们将去看看
it and see what this looks like so it
它和看看这是什么样子所以它
did not do it still showed it as white
没有这样做 它仍然显示为白色
so this looks different than what we had
所以这看起来和我们以前的不一样
we thought we were going to have
我们以为我们会有
transparency there but really it showed
那里是透明的 但实际上它显示了
up as white in our photo viewer and more
在我们的照片查看器中显示为白色以及更多
importantly on the desktop when we try
重要的是当我们尝试在桌面上
to zoom in and do what we did with the
要放大并执行我们对
icon we can't do it with this one
图标我们不能用这个来做
we just see these white corners so let's
我们只看到这些白色的角落 所以让我们
go back and let's do it the right way
回去吧 让我们以正确的方式来做
which is to go to file and we go to
那就是去申请 然后我们去
export as and then we change these last
导出为 然后我们更改这些最后一个
three letters to P n G it's just a
给P·N·G的三个字母这只是一个
different file format it processes the
它处理的文件格式不同
image different and PNG supports
不同的图像和PNG支持
transparent background there are
透明背景有
versions of there's ways you can have a
有几种方法可以让你拥有一个
transparent background with a JPEG but
透明背景 使用JPEG 但
the best thing to do is just always get
最好的办法就是
in the habit of exporting in a PNG file
习惯于以PNG文件格式导出
notice it's taking a little bit longer
请注意 这需要更长一点的时间
to export let's take a look here and see
要出口 让我们看看这里 看看
some of the differences between these
它们之间的一些区别
two so now we see this one is looking
两个 所以现在我们看到这个是在看
kind of weird I can zoom in a little bit
有点奇怪 我可以放大一点
it's gonna be a little bit grainy but we
它会有一点模糊 但我们
see this image doesn't have that white
你看这张照片没有那么白
it's sort of strange sort of a strange
这是一种奇怪的 一种奇怪的
image to make but that's the difference
制造形象 但这是不同的
between the two we have a jpg and a PNG
在这两者之间 我们有一个jpg和一个png
and let's right-click and go to I'll go
让我们右击并转到I‘ll Go
to properties on this one this one is
对于这一块的属性 这块是
kilobytes this one if we go to
这是千字节 如果我们转到
properties this one is 2 megabytes so
这个属性是2兆字节 所以
the JPEG is gonna be is going to be
JPEG将会是
smaller because it doesn't have as much
更小 因为它没有那么多
detail it's just white and then this one
细节 它只是白色 然后是这一个
has the transparency but it also
具有透明度 但它也
processes it processes the pixels a
处理它将像素处理为
little bit differently so this is about
有一点不同 所以这是关于
five times larger than this then the
比这个大五倍 那么
same image and there's ways we can
同样的形象 我们有办法
optimize that as well but just be aware
也要优化这一点 但请注意
when you're working in transparency when
当你在透明的环境中工作时
you add an alpha channel to an image it
您将Alpha通道添加到图像中
is going to increase the size ok let's
将会增加尺寸 好的 让我们来
go to let's look at another way that we
让我们来看看另一种方式 我们
could get an image if we erase we've
如果我们擦掉我们的图像就能得到图像
closed out of this if we want to start
如果我们想要开始的话
we go to file new we want to create a
我们转到新文件 我们想要创建一个
document with a transparent background
具有透明背景的文档
to start with well if we go 1920 by 1080
首先 如果我们从1920年到1080年
and we go ok it creates oh this one did
我们走好了 它创造了 哦 这一次做到了
it for us but that's because I was
对我们来说 但那是因为我
playing with it earlier for you go to
早些时候玩过它 你可以去
Advanced Options this option here is
高级选项此处的选项为
usually set to fill with background
通常设置为用背景填充
color and when you do that it whatever
颜色 当你这样做的时候 不管是什么
your background color is in this case
本例中为您的背景颜色
it's white for us it's this color right
对我们来说是白色的 是这个颜色对吗？
over here whatever is selected there
在这里 无论在那里选择了什么
when you create the new document it's
当您创建新文档时
going to create that as your background
我会把它作为你的背景
color it assumes you're working with a
颜色它假定您使用的是
blank white canvas and you want to
空白的白色画布 你想要
create art on top of that white canvas
在那块白色画布上创作艺术
or blue or red or whatever color you
或蓝色或红色或任何你喜欢的颜色
have selected there but if you want to
已经在那里选择了 但如果您想
create something like a logo like the
创建一些类似徽标的东西 例如
icon or you want to create
图标或您要创建的
something for our website it's a very
为我们的网站做点什么 这是一个非常
good idea to have transparency
保持透明度是个好主意
especially you want to create some
尤其是你想要创建一些
contour and some shape besides a
轮廓和一些形状
rectangle or square so to do that we go
长方形或正方形 所以我们要这样做
file new and then we click here under
提交新文件 然后我们单击此处
Advanced Options and then under the fill
高级选项 然后在填充下方
width we just say fill with the
宽度 我们只是说用
transparency and that'll automatically
透明度 这将自动地
give us a transparent background and
给我们一个透明的背景和
automatically add an alpha channel in
在中自动添加Alpha通道
there and so now we have a background
所以现在我们有了一个背景
here something people will do is they'll
在这里 人们会做的是 他们会
have a canvas like this they'll set up a
有了这样的画布 他们就会设立一个
blank background and then they'll
空白背景 然后他们就会
right-click over here and go new layer
在此处单击鼠标右键并转到新图层
and they'll have their second layer and
他们会有他们的第二层
they'll call this I don't know whatever
他们会说这是我不知道的
whatever they're drawing they'll call it
不管他们画什么 他们都会叫它
something over here and then they'll go
一些东西在这里 然后他们就会离开
and then you can also choose when you're
然后你也可以选择什么时候你是
creating a layer to fill it
创建一个层来填充它
with transparency or with white or with
透明的或白色的或
a specific pattern or with the
特定的图案或带有
background color foreground color but
背景色前景色 但
maybe you'll say fill it with white and
也许你会说 把它装满白色
then what you have is you still have a
那么你所拥有的就是你还有一个
white canvas you can still draw on here
你还可以在白色画布上画画
what's big you can still draw and do
什么是大的 你仍然可以画和做
whatever you wanted to but then when you
你想做什么就做什么 但当你
want to erase you'll still be able to
想要擦除 你仍然可以
erase if you wanted to you could erase
如果你想抹掉 你可以抹掉
some of that white canvas to reveal the
一些白色的画布展示了
true transparency behind it so again
它背后的真正透明度又是如此之高
real quick recap if we were to open up a
如果我们要打开一个
just an image from the desktop we
只是我们桌面上的一张图片
grabbed an image here we want to work
拍下了一张我们想要的照片
with it
带着它
we don't have transparency by default so
默认情况下我们没有透明度 所以
when we try to erase you races into
当我们试图抹掉你们的比赛时
white if we want to have transparency
如果我们想要有透明度 那就是白色
there you can also convert to if if you
在那里您还可以转换为IF 如果您
accidentally you started erasing and you
不小心你开始抹去 然后你
you forgot and realized oh I wanted all
你忘记了 并意识到 哦 我想要一切
this stuff to be transparent and you
这些东西是透明的 而你
don't want to have to undo an add an add
我不想撤消添加操作
transparency because if we add
透明度 因为如果我们添加
transparency now it's going to just be
透明度现在只会是
which now when we click it's going to be
现在 当我们点击它时 它将是
it but the stuff we already did isn't
但是我们已经做的事情并不是
happening or isn't transparent so one
发生的或不透明的所以一个
thing you can do is you can go up to
你能做的就是你可以去
colors and then you go down to color to
颜色 然后你再往下看颜色
alpha we wanted we don't want to adjust
我们想要的阿尔法 我们不想调整
yet because we need to select just a
然而 因为我们只需要选择一个
certain color so we could use like the
特定的颜色 这样我们就可以使用
magic wand selection we could select
魔杖精选 我们可以选择
this hold down shift it's like both of
这个按住变速键就像是两个
these and then we can go to colors and
这些 然后我们可以去颜色和
go to color to alpha and what that will
转到颜色为Alpha以及它将会是什么
do is turn everything within that
要做的就是把里面的一切
selected area and that is this specific
选定的区域 这是特定的
color it turns it to alpha so that adds
颜色会将其转换为Alpha 这样可以添加
it in there that's kind of a way to do
在那里 这是一种方法
it we could shrink and grow that maybe
如果我们可以缩小和增长 也许
that a little bit differently so that's
这有点不同 所以这是
just a quick look at transparency and
只需快速浏览一下透明度和
alpha we're going to be using it more in
阿尔法 我们将更多地使用它
future tutorials so I wanted to give a
未来的教程 所以我想给出一个
quick introduction let you play with it
快速介绍 让你玩它
a little bit and mostly learn how you
一点点 主要是了解你是如何
can get an alpha channel or how you can
可以获得Alpha通道 或者您可以
start working with transparency in
开始使用中的透明度
so hopefully found that informative
所以希望我能找到有用的信息
leave your questions or comments below
请在下面留下您的问题或评论
if you have any and I'll catch you in
如果你有的话 我会让你进去的
the next video
下一个视频